Uma Musume A
Hey hey, so what are ya gonna wear this year? Are you gonna be a witch? Or maybe... a black cat?
Uma Musume B
Jeez, stop messing around and help me with preparing the food! The ones in charge this year are...
Mihono Bourbon
...As it stands, the Ritto dormitory will be in charge of this year's joint dormitory Halloween party.
And it has been decided that I, Mihono Bourbon, will be the leader of the preparation committee.
I look forward to working with you all.
Tamamo Cross
And Creek and I'll be takin' care of the costumes! Everyone, let's do our best!!
Super Creek
The costumes will be made in collaboration with the school staff, so if anyone has a desired costume, please fill out the application form.
Tamamo Cross
Anyways, Bourbon, this yer first time bein' in charge, ain't it? Anythin' worryin ya?
Last year Inari was put in charge of Miho.
That sure was a mess, huh...
Mihono Bourbon
There is no problem. My mission of ordering sweets for the joint dormitory Halloween party has already concluded.
Continuing with last year's theme, I have also ordered a smoke machine, which has already arrived.
It will be loaned out to the operation's management committee once a thorough analysis has been conducted.
Super Creek
Wow. Bourbon-chan, you're doing as
great a job as ever.
Mihono Bourbon
However, when I attempted to turn the smoke machine on in order to conduct a test run, no smoke came out.
Therefore, one can reasonably
conclude that there is a possibility...
Kyaaaaa!?
Waaaahhh!?
Mihono Bourbon
Cough... I was worried that there
might be some adverse side effects.
However, since the smoke consists mainly of water vapor, there should be no harm... Cough.
Tamamo Cross
...You sure yer okay?
Preparations began for the
joint dormitory Halloween party.
The leader of the preparation committee,
Mihono Bourbon was...
Mihono Bourbon
Butter for the cooking
committee has been acquired.
Now I must acquire some light bulbs
for the equipment committee.
Afterwards, I need to prepare a time table for the information committee, then contact the costume committee, then...
Mihono Bourbon
...Manufacturing of a spare jack-o-lantern has failed. Therefore, I will prepare this pumpkin as a meal for myself instead...
Preparation of explanatory materials in progress.
The Tracen Academy Halloween event
was created for international students.
However, the event focuses on
entertainment rather than nostalgia......
Zenno Rob Roy
Bourbon-san...
She seems so busy...
After all, the joint dormitory Halloween
party is going to be incredibly large...
But if we offer to help her without knowing what we're doing, it will just end up causing her to have more work...
Rice Shower
............
Zenno Rob Roy
Rice-san?
Rice Shower
Ah... S-Sorry...
I... agree with you...
...I really do...
But...
Rice Shower
(I wonder if that pumpkin is the failed
jack-o-lantern that she had mentioned...)
Mihono Bourbon
All that is left of this pumpkin is... 15kg 600g...
This should keep me hydrated...
Ritto Student
Hey... Bourbon-san.
Would you like our help finishing that?
Mihono Bourbon
I refuse. You all have your
own tasks at hand currently.
Not to mention that this is the result of my failure, therefore, I should resolve it on my own.
Tamamo Cross
Hmm? Rice, people've been lining up behind you for a while now, ya know? If ya want a carrot hamburg steak feel free and get one.
Rice Shower
Whaa!? Sorry, I am so sorry!
I didn't realize that I had lined up... Umm...
Tamamo Cross
What? Got somethin' to say to Bourbon?
Then why doncha just tell her? Go on now.
Tamamo Cross
Bourbon, excuse me.
Rice's got somethin' to talk to you about.
Rice Shower
N-No... I...
can't... say it...
Tamamo Cross
Eh!? Wastin' time by not sayin' anythings just gonna make it harder to say, ya know?
Just start the conversation off with somethin' simple. Like how bout the weather?
Rice Shower
Eeh!? W-Well... Err, umm...
To... today's weather sure is great, isn't it...?
Mihono Bourbon
I agree, it is sunny today.
...............
Tamamo Cross
Eh...? What's with the tension here?
Is this a blind date?
Super Creek
Ara ara...
And so the preparations for the Tracen Academy joint dormitory Halloween party began in earnest.
Will the girls truly be able to pull it off?
That night...
Kyaaaa!!
There was a scream so loud
it could deafen the gods above...